Bryan J. Ralphs

Salt Lake City, UT | 801.666.0456 | bryan.j.ralphs@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/bryan-j-ralphs

OBJECTIVE

Award-winning professional with experience spanning from fintech to healthtech. 4+ years of academic and professional experience in the development of software solutions. Ambitiously pursuing software engineering positions to leverage software as a means to magnify human potential.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Software Developer

Jan 2023 - Present

Wixcorp – Riverton, UT

- Develop full-stack applications and ensure compatibility with its integrated database
- Maintain, test, and debug software modules across the Wixcorp suite
- Leverage knowledge in C#, .NET Framework, SQL, Azure Data Studio, and Agile Methodologies

Credit Specialist

Jun 2021 - Aug 2023

Lending Club - Lehi, UT

- Performed comprehensive analyses of client applications to ascertain eligibility
- Maintained the compliance of assigned applications with federal and lender criteria

Client Relationship Consultant

Mar 2019 - Jun 2021

U.S. BANCORP - Orem, UT

- Managed sales and marketing of consumer accounts, business accounts, and credit products
- Received notary license, originated loans, and managed transactions

Peak-Time Teller

Mar 2018 - Mar 2019

U.S. BANCORP - Orem, UT

Provided customer service, transaction handling, sale and advertisement of credit cards

Center Consultant

Nov 2017 – Mar 2018

FedEx Office - Orem, UT

Organized product management, and provided customer service, retail, and print production

SKILLS

- Python (proficient)
- AWS (familiar)

Java (proficient)

- HTML/CSS (proficient)
- C#/.NET (proficient)
- Conflict Resolution

- JavaScript (proficient)
- SQL (familiar)

• Presenting & Public Speaking

- Linux OS (familiar)
- Git/Github (familiar)
- Spanish Language (proficient)

EDUCATION